Howard W. and Jean Lipman
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Howard and Jean Lipman Art Collection, 1954-2000, undated, Series 2:; (Boxes 3-15, 12 linear feet)
  - Sculpture Collection Purchases, 1954-1989, undated, 2.2:
    - Chryssa, Varda, 1961-1973, undated (Box 5)
    - Cohen, George, 1963-1965 (Box 5)
    - Cornell, Joseph, 1962-1976, undated (Box 5)
    - Conner, Bruce, 1960-1976, undated (Box 5)
    - De Forest, Ray, 1959-1972, undated (Box 5)
    - De Maria, Walter, 1968-1979, undated (Box 5)
    - De Moulpied, Deborah, 1962-1965 (Box 5)
    - De Rivera, Jose, 1956-1978, undated (Box 5)
    - Dehner, Dorothy, 1959-1972, undated (Box 5)
    - DeLap, Tony, 1963-1974, undated (Box 5)
    - Di Suvero, Mark, 1960-1979, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Durchanek, Ludvik, 1958-1966 (Box 5)
    - Engman, Robert M., 1960-1978, undated (Box 5)
    - Ferber, Herbert, 1957-1980, undated (Box 5)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1964-1979, undated (Box 5)
    - Frazier, Paul, 1964-1968 (Box 5)
    - Gilardi, Pero, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Gill, James, 1963-1966 (Box 5)
    - Glasco, Joseph, 1959-1965, undated (Box 5)
    - Goodyear, John, 1963-1966, undated (Box 5)
    - Gordin, Sidney, 1960-1962, undated (Box 5)
    - Gostomski, Zbigniew, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Grossman, Nancy, 1968-1975, undated (Box 5)
    - Hadzi, Dimitri, 1959-1978, undated (Box 5)
    - Hague, Raoul, 1960-circa 1975, undated (Box 5)
    - Hale, Nathan Cabot, 1960-1973, undated (Box 5)
    - Hardy, Tom, 1955-1978, undated (Box 5)
    - Higgins, Edward, 1960-1966, undated (Box 5)
    - Indiana, Robert, 1962-1982, undated (Box 5)
    - Johnson, Ray, 1963-1977, undated (Box 5)
    - Judd, Donald, 1963-1979, undated (Box 5)
    - Kauffman, Craig, 1967-1973 (Box 5)
    - Kauppi, Tauno, 1962-1965, undated (Box 5)
    - Kearns, James, 1959-1973, undated (Box 5)
    - Keisler, Frederick, 1964-1976, undated (Box 5)
    - Kienholz, Edward, 1961-1975, undated (Box 6)
    - King, William, 1954-1974, undated (Box 6)
    - Kipp, Lyman, 1960-1974, undated (Box 6)
    - Konzal, Joseph, 1959-1978, undated (Box 6)
    - Kussoy, Bernice, 1961-1967, undated (Box 6)
    - Lamis, Leroy, 1963-1975, undated (Box 6)
    - Lassaw, Ibram, 1958-1970, undated (Box 6)
    - Liberman, Alexander, 1962-1979, undated (Box 6)
    - Lippold, Richard, 1962-1973, undated (Box 6)
    - Lipton, Seymour, 1958-1971, undated (Box 6)
    - Mallory, Ronald, 1966-1972, undated (Box 6)
    - Morris, Robert, 1964-1980, undated (Box 6)
    - Nash, Katherine, 1957-1961, undated (Box 6)
    - Neal, Reginald, 1965-1968, undated (Box 6)
    - Neuberger, Roy R., 1962, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Nevelson, Louise, 1963-1980, undated (Box 6)
    - Nevelson, Mike, 1961-1978, undated (Box 6)
    - Nivola, Constantino, 1954-1973 (Box 6)
    - Noguchi, Isamu, 1959-1980, undated (Box 6)
    - Odza, Theodore, 1964-1969 (Box 6)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1961-1980, undated (Box 6)
    - Ossorio, Alfonso, 1962-1972, undated (Box 6)
    - Padovano, Anthony, 1964-1978, undated (Box 6)
    - Pettibone, Richard, 1964-1970 (Box 6)
    - Price, Kenneth, 1964-1980, undated (Box 6)
    - Reimann, William, 1962-1965 (Box 6)
    - Rickey, George, 1959-1979, undated (Box 6)
    - Samaras, Lucas, 1963-1978, undated (Box 6)
    - Sandback, Fred, 1968-1976, undated (Box 6)
    - Schmidt, Julius, 1961-1966, undated (Box 6)
    - Segal, George, 1959-1980, undated (Box 7)
    - Seley, Jason, 1963-1978, undated (Box 7)
    - Smith, David, 1973-1980, undated (Box 7)
    - Smithson, Robert, 1966-1976, undated (Box 7)
    - Squier, Jack, 1956-1966 (Box 7)
    - Stankiewicz, Richard, 1956-1980, undated (Box 7)
    - Steiner, Michael, 1967-1980 (Box 7)
    - Talbot, William, 1963-1972 (Box 7)
    - Townley, Hugh, 1956-1969, undated (Box 7)
    - Trova, Ernest, 1965-1978, undated (Box 7)
    - Von Schlegell, David, 1963-1977, undated (Box 7)
    - Voulkos, Peter, 1960-1975, undated (Box 7)
    - Weinberg, Elbert, 1955-1975, undated (Box 7)
    - Wesselmann, Tom, 1962-1979 (Box 7)
    - Westermann, H.C., 1958-1978, undated (Box 7)
    - Westermann, Joanna, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Wilmarth, Christopher, 1968-1978, undated (Box 7)
    - Wines, James, 1960-1968, undated (Box 7)
  - Sculptors of Interest, 1950-1980, undated, 2.3:
    The documents within this subseries consist of information about artists whose works and careers were followed by the Howard W. Lipman Foundation. The material includes biographical information, correspondence, announcements and invitations to exhibitions, reviews, press releases, and other miscellaneous printed items. Arrangement within the subseries is alphabetical, by surname of the artist. Documents within folders are arranged chronologically by year, but in folders that contain large amounts of acidic printed material, such as newspaper clippings, these materials are grouped together in chronological order by year and isolated from the other documents by acid-free barriers at the rear of the folder.
    - Acconi, Vito, 1972-1977 (Box 7)
    - Adams, Robert, 1961-1974 (Box 7)
    - Adamy, George, 1966-1971 (Box 7)
    - Agam, Yaacov, 1966, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Ajay, Ibraham Mahfoud, 1964-circa 1975, undated (Box 7)
    - Alex, Kosta, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
    - Alexander, Peter, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
    - Amato, Anthony, 1968-1972 (Box 7)
    - Anastasi, William, 1966, 1970 (Box 7)
    - Anderson, Jeremy, 1961-1962, undated (Box 7)
    - Andre, Carl, 1965-1978, undated (Box 7)
    - Andrews, Oliver, 1955-1975, undated (Box 7)
    - Apple, Billy (aka Barrie Bates), 1967 (Box 7)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 1959-1973, undated (Box 7)
    - Arman (aka Armand Pierre Fernandez or Armand Pierre Arman), 1969-1973 (Box 7)
    - Armitage, Kenneth, 1952-1963, undated (Box 7)
    - Arneson, Robert, 1970-1980, undated (Box 7)
    - Arnold, Anne, 1960-1979, undated (Box 7)
    - Arnoldi, Charles, 1974-1975 (Box 7)
    - Aronson, David, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Arp, Jean, 1969-1976 (Box 7)
    - A, Miscellaneous Artists, 1963-1975, undated (Box 7)
    - Baizerman, Saul, 1963-1972 (Box 7)
    - Bakaty, Mike, 1970-1973 (Box 7)
    - Baldacinni, Cesar (aka Cesar), 1961, undated (Box 7)
    - Ballaine, Jerrold, 1967-1968, undated (Box 7)
    - Bang, Thomas, 1969-1978, undated (Box 7)
    - Barlach, Ernst, 1962, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Barron, Harris, 1962-1965 (Box 7)
    - Baschet, Bernard and Francois, 1967-1971, undated (Box 7)
    - Bauermeister, Mary, 1967-1972 (Box 7)
    - Beasley, Bruce, 1964-1972 (Box 8)
    - Behl, Wolfgang, 1968-1973 (Box 8)
    - Benazzi, Raffael, 1963-1968 (Box 8)
    - Benglis, Lynda, 1969-1980, undated (Box 8)
    - Bennett, John, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Benoff, Miki, 1970, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Berdyszak, Jan, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
    - Berrocal, Miguel, 1969-1970, undated (Box 8)
    - Beuys, Joseph, 1973-1975, undated (Box 8)
    - Bill, Max, 1962-1970, undated (Box 8)
    - Bladen, Ronald, 1962-1978, undated (Box 8)
    - Bleifeld, Stanley, 1963, 1972 (Box 8)
    - Bollinger, William, 1966-1976, undated (Box 8)
    - Boterf, Check, 1968-1974, undated (Box 8)
    - Bourdelle, Antoine, 1964-1970 (Box 8)
    - Bourgeous, Louise, 1961-1980, undated (Box 8)
    - Boxer, Stanley, 1968-1978 (Box 8)
    - Boyce, Richard, 1960-1969, undated (Box 8)
    - Brancusi, Constantin, 1960-1969 (Box 8)
    - Breer, Robert, 1965-1970 (Box 8)
    - Brose, Morris, 1960-1965 (Box 8)
    - Brown, David Lee, 1970-1973 (Box 8)
    - Brown, Judith, 1963-1968 (Box 8)
    - Brown, Paul, 1970 (Box 8)
    - Buchman, James, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Bultman, Fritz, 1963-1977 (Box 8)
    - Buren, Daniel, 1973-1975 (Box 8)
    - Bury, Pol, 1964-1973, undated (Box 8)
    - Butler, Reg, 1962-1973, undated (Box 8)
    - B, Miscellaneous Artists, 1959-1977, undated, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Callery, Mary, 1950-1966 (Box 8)
    - Campbell, Kenneth, 1962-1966, undated (Box 8)
    - Caparn, Rhys, 1961-1977, undated (Box 8)
    - Caro, Anthony, 1964-1977 (Box 8)
    - Cascella, Andrea, 1965-1972 (Box 8)
    - Chase, Doris, 1969-1973, undated (Box 8)
    - Chillida, Eduardo, 1968-1969, undated (Box 8)
    - Chinni, Peter, 1961-1969, undated (Box 8)
    - Christo (Favacheff, Christo), 1967-1973, undated (Box 8)
    - Collie, Alberto, 1964-1967 (Box 8)
    - Consagra, Pietro, 1962-1965, undated (Box 8)
    - Cook, Robert, 1953-1966, undated (Box 8)
    - Cremean, Robert, 1959-1976 (Box 8)
    - Cronbach, Robert, 1961-1971 (Box 8)
    - C, Miscellaneous Artists, 1959-1978, undated, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Dallegret, Francois, 1966 (Box 8)
    - De Andrea, John, 1971-1973 (Box 8)
    - De Creeft, Jose, 1961-1975, undated (Box 8)
    - De Kooning, Willem, 1972-1975, undated (Box 8)
    - De Maria, Walter, 1968, undated (Box 8)
    - Decker, Lindsey, 1959-1967, n.d (Box 8)
    - Delonga, Leonard, 1961-1976 (Box 8)
    - Dill, Guy, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
    - Diller, Burgoyne, 1964-1971, undated (Box 8)
    - Dine, Jim, 1962-1973, undated (Box 8)
    - Dix, Harry, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Doyle, Tom, 1961-1978, undated (Box 8)
    - Dubin, William, 1966-1968 (Box 8)
    - Dubuffet, Jean, 1968-1974 (Box 9)
    - Duca, Alfred, 1961-1962, undated (Box 9)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
    - Duff, John, 1970-1978 (Box 9)
    - Duran, Robert, 1966-1971 (Box 9)
    - Dusenberry, Walter, 1970-1973, undated (Box 9)
    - D, Miscellaneous Artists, 1959-1974, undated (Box 9)
    - Edlich, Stephen, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
    - Edwards, Mel, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
    - Eloul, Kosso, 1965-1971 (Box 9)
    - Ernst, Max, 1965, 1971, undated (Box 9)
    - Escobar, Marisol ("Marisol"), 1964-1974, undated (Box 9)
    - Etrog, Sorel, 1963-1972 (Box 9)
    - Eversley, Frederick, 1970-1980 (Box 9)
    - E, Miscellaneous Artists, 1959-1973 (Box 9)
    - Falkenstein, Claire, 1959-1976, undated (Box 9)
    - FeBland, Harriet, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Feeley, Paul, 1964-1973, undated (Box 9)
    - Ferrara, Jackie, 1973-1979 (Box 9)
    - Ferrer, Rafael, 1970-1980, undated (Box 9)
    - Filipovic, Augustin, 1969-1973 (Box 9)
    - Filipowski, Richard, 1964-1974 (Box 9)
    - Finkelstein, Mike, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Finklestein, Max, 1967-1970, undated (Box 9)
    - Fitzgerald, James, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Forakis, Peter, 1966, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Frank, Mary, 1962-1979, undated (Box 9)
    - Frazier, Charles, 1964-1965, undated (Box 9)
    - Fredericks, Marshall, 1962, undated (Box 9)
    - Friedeberg, Pedro, 1966, 1971, undated (Box 9)
    - Frink, Elizabeth, 1961-1966, undated (Box 9)
    - Fuller, Sue, 1961-1969 (Box 9)
    - F, Miscellaneous Artists, 1961-1976, undated (Box 9)
    - Gabo, Naum, 1966-1968 (Box 9)
    - Gallo, Frank, 1965-1972, undated (Box 9)
    - George, Herbert, 1966-1972 (Box 9)
    - Giacometti, Alberto, 1964-1976, undated (Box 9)
    - Gianakos, Cristos, 1968-1972 (Box 9)
    - Ginnever, Charles, 1966-1980, undated (Box 9)
    - Gonzales, Julio, 1965-1976, undated (Box 9)
    - Goto, Joseph, 1964-1973, undated (Box 9)
    - Goulet, Lorrie, 1962-1968 (Box 9)
    - Graham, Robert, 1967-1977 (Box 9)
    - Granlund, Paul, 1963-1965, undated (Box 9)
    - Grausman, Philip, 1966-1979 (Box 9)
    - Graves, Nancy, 1969-1980, undated (Box 9)
    - Gray, Cleve, 1964-1975, undated (Box 9)
    - Gray, David, 1966, 1969, undated (Box 9)
    - Greenleaf, Ken, 1973-1981 (Box 9)
    - Greenly, Colin, 1963-1974, undated (Box 9)
    - Grooms, Red, 1970-1975, undated (Box 9)
    - Gross, Chaim, 1962-1974, undated (Box 9)
    - Grosvenor, Robert, 1965-1978, undated (Box 9)
    - Guerriero, Henry, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Gussow, Roy, 1964-1980, undated (Box 9)
    - Gutkin, Peter, 1974-1975, undated (Box 9)
    - G, Miscellaneous Artists, 1959-1976, undated, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Haacke, Hans, 1966-1977, undated (Box 10)
    - Haber, Ira Joel, 1971-1978 (Box 10)
    - Halem, Henry, 1968-1969 (Box 10)
    - Hall, Michael, 1970-1972, undated (Box 10)
    - Halkin, Theodore, undated (Box 10)
    - Hansen, Duane, 1970-1978, undated (Box 10)
    - Hatchett, Duane, 1969-1975, undated (Box 10)
    - Hare, David, 1976-1977, undated (Box 10)
    - Harris, Paul, 1965-1973, undated (Box 10)
    - Hayes, David V., 1957-1971 (Box 10)
    - Hebald, Milton, 1959-1973 (Box 10)
    - Heiliger, Bernhard, 1961-1970 (Box 10)
    - Heiser, Michael, 1969-1980 (Box 10)
    - Helfant, Nancy, 1967-1969 (Box 10)
    - Henghes, Henry, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Hepworth, Barbara, circa 1955-1974, undated (Box 10)
    - Hesse, Eva, 1968-1977, undated (Box 10)
    - Hokanson, Hans, 1965-1972 (Box 10)
    - Holland, Tom, 1970, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Hollingworth, Keith, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
    - Honegger, Gottfried, 1963-1964, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Horwitt, Will, 1963-1977 (Box 10)
    - Howard, Robert, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
    - Hudson, Robert, 1965-1979, undated (Box 10)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1968-1972, undated (Box 10)
    - Hunt, Richard, 1958-1971, undated (Box 10)
    - Huntington, Jim, 1972-1980, undated (Box 10)
    - Hutchinson, Peter, 1967-1977 (Box 10)
    - H, Miscellaneous Artists, 1961-1981, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Ihlenfeld, Klaus, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Insley, Will, 1967-1974, undated (Box 10)
    - Ipousteguy, Jean Robert, 1964-1972, undated (Box 10)
    - Irwin, Robert, 1968-1977 (Box 10)
    - Israel, Margaret, 1971-1976 (Box 10)
    - I, Miscellaneous Artists, 1965-1973 (Box 10)
    - Jackson, Harry, 1960-1980, undated (Box 10)
    - Jacobs, David, 1963-1967, undated (Box 10)
    - Jacobs, Joan, 1961-1962 (Box 10)
    - Jacobsen, Robert, 1962-1966 (Box 10)
    - Jimenez, Luis A., 1969-1979 (Box 10)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1969-1977, undated (Box 10)
    - Jones, Howard, 1966-1974 (Box 10)
    - Jorgensen, Roger, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
    - J, Miscellaneous Artists, 1964-1973, undated (Box 10)
    - Kaish, Luise, 1968-1969 (Box 10)
    - Kallem, Herbert, 1962, 1967 (Box 10)
    - Kanovitz, Howard, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Katzen, Lila, 1968-circa 1980, undated (Box 10)
    - Kearl, Stanley, 1962-1968 (Box 10)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1963-1980, undated (Box 10)
    - Kemeny, Zoltan, 1959, 1968, undated (Box 10)
    - Kirschenbaum, Bernard, 1967-1977 (Box 10)
    - Klavun, Betty, 1968-1972 (Box 10)
    - Knoop, Guitou, 1962-1967, undated (Box 10)
    - Koenig, Fritz, 1961-1972 (Box 10)
    - Kohn, Gabriel, 1961-1972, undated (Box 10)
    - Kosice, Gyula, 1965-1967 (Box 10)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1970-1974 (Box 10)
    - Krentzin, Earl, 1960-1968 (Box 10)
    - Kruger, Louise, 1958-1970 (Box 10)
    - Krugman, Irene, 1969-1973 (Box 10)
    - Kuehn, Gary, 1966-1974, undated (Box 10)
    - Kuehn, George, 1971-1978 (Box 10)
    - Kuriloff, Aaron, 1965-1967, undated (Box 10)
    - Kusama, Yayoi, 1964-1966 (Box 10)
    - K, Miscellaneous Artists, circa 1958-1974, undated (Box 10)
    - K, Miscellaneous Artists, circa 1958-1974, undated (Box 11)
    - Lachaise, Gaston, 1964-1971, undated (Box 11)
    - Laing, Gerald, 1965-1968 (Box 11)
    - Langlais, Bernard, 1962-1971, undated (Box 11)
    - Laurens, Henri, 1958-1971 (Box 11)
    - Laurent, Robert, 1962, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Le Va, Barry, 1973-1977 (Box 11)
    - Lekakis, Michael, 1960-1973, undated (Box 11)
    - Leon, Dennis, 1966-1970 (Box 11)
    - Levine, Les, 1968-1974, undated (Box 11)
    - Levinson, Mon, 1964-1976 (Box 11)
    - Levitan, Israel, 1959-1964, undated (Box 11)
    - Lew, Jeffrey, 1970-1975 (Box 11)
    - Lewitt, Sol, 1966-1978, undated (Box 11)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1967-1977 (Box 11)
    - Light, Alvin, 1965, undated (Box 11)
    - Liikala, Bob, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Linder, Jean, 1966-1976, undated (Box 11)
    - Lipchitz, Jacques, 1957-1973 (Box 11)
    - Lipman-Wulf, Peter, 1966-1973 (Box 11)
    - Littleton, Harvey, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Lloyd, Tom, 1965-1968, undated (Box 11)
    - Lobe, Robert, 1969-1980, undated (Box 11)
    - Lobello, Peter, 1977, undated (Box 11)
    - Long, Richard, 1969-1977 (Box 11)
    - Love, Jim, 1964-1980 (Box 11)
    - Lovet-Lorski, Boris, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - Lucchesi, Bruno, 1961-1971 (Box 11)
    - Lukin, Sven, 1966-1970 (Box 11)
    - Lye, Bix, 1963-1964, undated (Box 11)
    - Lye, Len, 1961-1965 (Box 11)
    - L, Miscellaneous Artists, 1951-1976, undated (Box 11)
    - Maillol, Aristide, 1970-1976 (Box 11)
    - Maliary, Robert, 1961-1977 (Box 11)
    - Manzu, Gaicomo, 1964-1972, undated (Box 11)
    - Marca-Relli, Conrad, 1963-1964 (Box 11)
    - Marcks, Gerhard, 1958-1971 (Box 11)
    - Mark, Phyllis, 1968-1973 (Box 11)
    - Marshall, John, 1967, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Martinelli, Ezio 1959-1966, undated (Box 11)
    - Mastroianni, Umberto, 1960-1964 (Box 11)
    - Matisse, Henri, 1958-1972, undated (Box 11)
    - Mattox, Charles, 1965-1974, undated (Box 11)
    - McCracken, John, circa 1966-1973 (Box 11)
    - McCracken, Philip, 1960-1970 (Box 11)
    - McDowell, Barrie, 1963-1968, undated (Box 11)
    - Meadmore, Clement, 1968-1973, undated (Box 11)
    - Meadows, Bernard, 1959-1964 (Box 11)
    - Meyer, Ursula, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
    - Milkowski, Tony, 1966-1970 (Box 11)
    - Miller, Richard, 1966-1975 (Box 11)
    - Minguzzi, Luciano, 1961-1969, undated (Box 11)
    - Miro, Joan, 1970-1976 (Box 11)
    - Miss, Mary, 1971-1975 (Box 11)
    - Mondrian, Piet, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Moore, Henry, 1959-1972, undated (Box 11)
    - Morrel, Marc, 1966-1970, undated (Box 11)
    - Morton, Ree, 1974-1977, undated (Box 11)
    - Muir, William, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Murray, Robert, 1965-1980, undated (Box 11)
    - Myers, Forrest, 1965-1970, undated (Box 11)
    - M, Miscellaneous Artists, 1959-1974, undated, (3 folders) (Box 12)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 1961-1975, undated (Box 12)
    - Nagare, Masayuki, 1963-1974, undated (Box 12)
    - Nakian, Reuben, 1958-1979, undated (Box 12)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1969-1978, undated (Box 12)
    - Negret, Edgar, 1966-1974, undated (Box 12)
    - Newman, Barnett, 1966-1971 (Box 12)
    - Neuman, Howard, 1975-1979 (Box 12)
    - Nickford, Juan, 1956-1974 (Box 12)
    - Nizuma, Minoru, 1966-1974 (Box 12)
    - Nonas, Richard, 1973-1977 (Box 12)
    - Novak, Gyora (Giora), 1972 (Box 12)
    - N, Miscellaneous Artists, 1960-1976, undated (Box 12)
    - Odate, Toshio, 1963-1969 (Box 12)
    - O'Doherty, Brian, 1970-1977 (Box 12)
    - Okulick, John, 1973-1980 (Box 12)
    - Olitski, Jules, 1969-1973 (Box 12)
    - Oppenheim, Dennis, 1968-1979, undated (Box 12)
    - Orr, Olen, 1968-1980, undated (Box 12)
    - Ortman, George, 1960-1976, undated (Box 12)
    - Owen, Warren, 1967-1973 (Box 12)
    - O, Miscellaneous Artists, 1961-1963, undated (Box 12)
    - Paik, Nam June, 1969-1975, undated (Box 12)
    - Paolozzi, Eduardo, 1962-1967 (Box 12)
    - Paris, Harold, 1969-1975, undated (Box 12)
    - Pattison, Abbott, 1959, 1966 (Box 12)
    - Pavia, Philip, 1961-1969, undated (Box 12)
    - Pearson, Louis, 1973, undated (Box 12)
    - Pepper, Beverly, 1962-1980, undated (Box 12)
    - Perry, Charles O., 1968-1970, undated (Box 12)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 1957-1980, undated (Box 12)
    - Piene, Otto, 1965-1971, undated (Box 12)
    - Pomodoro, Arnaldo and Gio, 1965-1977, undated (Box 12)
    - Porter, Stephen, Porter, Stephen (Box 12)
    - Potts, Don, 1970-1972 (Box 12)
    - Powell, Fred, 1959, 1961, undated (Box 12)
    - Prince, Roger, 1960-1970 (Box 12)
    - P, Miscellaneous Artists, 1959-1974, undated (Box 12)
    - Randell, Richard, 1966-1971 (Box 12)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1965-1980 (Box 12)
    - Reder, Bernard, 1959-1961, undated (Box 12)
    - Reginato, Peter, 1971-1980 (Box 12)
    - Reiback, Earl, 1967-1973 (Box 12)
    - Rennels, Sig, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
    - Renouf, Edward and Edda, 1962-1977, undated (Box 12)
    - Riboud, Barbara Chase, 1970-1972 (Box 12)
    - Richardson, Sam, 1968-1980, undated (Box 12)
    - Richter, Vjenceslav, 1968 (Box 12)
    - von Ringelheim, Paul, 1964-1978, undated (Box 12)
    - Rivers, Larry, 1959, 1973, undated (Box 12)
    - Robus, Hugo, 1960-1961, undated (Box 12)
    - Rocklin, Raymond, circa 1955, 1960, undated (Box 12)
    - Rodin, Auguste, 1963 (Box 12)
    - Rohm, Robert, 1963-1977, undated (Box 13)
    - Romano, Salvatore, 1968-1977 (Box 13)
    - Rosati, James, 1959-1970, undated (Box 13)
    - Rosenthal, Bernard, 1958-1969, undated (Box 13)
    - Ross, Charles, 1967-1977, undated (Box 13)
    - Rosso, Medardo, 1959, undated (Box 13)
    - Roszak, Theodore, 1962, 1974-1978, undated (Box 13)
    - R, Miscellaneous Artists, 1950-1977, undated (Box 13)
    - De Saint-Phalle, Niki, 1965-1979, undated (Box 13)
    - Saret, Alan, 1967-1980 (Box 13)
    - Satoru, Abe, 1961, 1965 (Box 13)
    - Scanga, Italo, 1967-1980 (Box 13)
    - Scarfe, Gerald, 1970 (Box 13)
    - Schanker, Louis, 1964-1973 (Box 13)
    - Schlemowitz, Abram, 1961-1962, undated (Box 13)
    - Scholl, John, 1967-1968 (Box 13)
    - Scott, Tim, 1969-1977 (Box 13)
    - Seawright, James, 1966-1975, undated (Box 13)
    - Secunda, Arthur, 1964, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Selig, Mike, 1971-1980, undated (Box 13)
    - Sellers, William, 1968-1973 (Box 13)
    - Serra, Richard, 1969-1980 (Box 13)
    - Shapiro, Joel, 1970-1977 (Box 13)
    - Shemi, Yehiel, 1973-1975 (Box 13)
    - Shields, Alan, 1972-1978 (Box 13)
    - Simon, Sidney, 1959-1978, undated (Box 13)
    - Slivka, David, 1961-1962, undated (Box 13)
    - Smith, Tony, 1966-1979, undated (Box 13)
    - Smyth, David, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Snelson, Kenneth, 1967-1979, undated (Box 13)
    - Snow, Michael, 1968-1972 (Box 13)
    - Soffer, Sasson, 1964-1973 (Box 13)
    - Soleri, Paolo, 1963, 1970 (Box 13)
    - Somaini, Francesco, 1962-1964, undated (Box 13)
    - Sonnier, Keith (Box 13)
    - Soto, Jesus, 1969, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Spaventa, George, 1959-1964 (Box 13)
    - Stella, Frank, 1975-1979 (Box 13)
    - Stern, Jan Peter, 1960-1967, undated (Box 13)
    - Stone, Sylvia, 1969-1979 (Box 13)
    - Storrs, John, 1965-1972 (Box 13)
    - Streeter, Tal, 1966-1976, undated (Box 13)
    - Sugarman, George, 1959-1975, undated (Box 13)
    - Swarz, Jahl, 1954-1966 (Box 13)
    - S, Miscellaneous Artists, 1958-1976, undated, (3 folders) (Box 13)
    - Tajiri, Shinkichi (See same series, Vassilakis, Panayiotis), 1958-1965, undated (Box 13)
    - Talbert, Ben, 1964-1965 (Box 13)
    - Tarr, William, 1963-1972 (Box 13)
    - Thek, Paul, 1966-1970, undated (Box 13)
    - Tinguely, Jean, circa 1959-1966 (Box 13)
    - Tobias, Julius, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Todd, Michael, 1964, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Torffield, Marvin, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
    - Tovish, Harold, 1965-circa 1973 (Box 13)
    - Trajan, Turku, 1959-1970 (Box 13)
    - Troller, Fred, 1965, 1968, undated (Box 13)
    - Truitt, Anne, 1963-1980 (Box 13)
    - Tsai, Wen-Ying, 1968-1972, undated (Box 13)
    - Turnbull, William, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Turrell, Jim, 1967-1969, undated (Box 13)
    - Tuttle, Richard, 1965-1975, undated (Box 14)
    - T, Miscellaneous Artists, 1958-1973, undated (Box 14)
    - Udinotti, Agnese, 1971-1974, undated (Box 14)
    - Uecker, Gunther, 1964, 1966 (Box 14)
    - Urry, Steve, 1967-1973 (Box 14)
    - U, Miscellaneous Artists, 1965-1973 (Box 14)
    - Valentine, Dewain, 1973-1975, undated (Box 14)
    - Van Buren, Richard, 1966-1977 (Box 14)
    - Van Saun, John, 1967-1971 (Box 14)
    - Vassilakis, Panayiotis (aka Takis), 1960-1970, undated (Box 14)
    - Viner, Frank Lincoln, 1971-1974 (Box 14)
    - Vollmer, Ruth, 1963-1977 (Box 14)
    - V, Miscellaneous Artists, 1958-1978, undated (Box 14)
  - Painters of Interest, 1955-1978, undated, 2.4:
    The documents within this subseries consist of information about artists whose works and careers were followed by the Howard W. Lipman Foundation, and include biographical material; correspondence; announcements and invitations to exhibitions; reviews; press releases, and other miscellaneous printed material.
    - D'Arista, Robert, 1955-1964 (Box 14)
    - Davis, Stuart, 1964-1965 (Box 14)
    - De Kooning, Willem, 1969-1972 (Box 14)
    - Eilshemius, Louis, 1959-1978, undated (Box 14)
    - Hartigan, Grace G., 1956, 1965 (Box 14)